degreescout.com 2014-11-21

# Privacy Policy | Online MBA

The privacy practices of this statement apply to our services available under the domain and sub-domains of DegreeScout. Please note that this Privacy Policy applies only to sites maintained by DegreeScout and not to websites maintained by other companies or organizations to which we link. In addition, this Policy applies only to information collected by DegreeScout online, not offline. By visiting our websites you agree to be bound by the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree please do not use or access our services.

Although this Policy may seem long, we have prepared a detailed policy because we believe you should know as much as possible about DegreeScout practices and how we treat any personal information that you may submit to us so that you can make an informed decision.

DegreeScout reserves the right to modify, amend or otherwise alter the terms of this Privacy Policy at any time, and without notice. All users of this site will be bound by the terms of this Privacy Policy and any subsequent modifications, amendments or alterations thereto.

At DegreeScout, information is the cornerstone of our ability to provide superior service. Our most important asset is our clients’ trust. We understand that you entrust us with your private information to allow you find match with one or more members of our business partner network which could include a bank, insurance provider, lender, loan broker or some other financial professional who may be able to meet your needs by responding to your inquiry (each a “Client” and collectively our “Clients”). Keeping your information secure, and using it only as you would want us to, is a top priority for all of us at DegreeScout.

  * We will safeguard, according to strict standards of security and confidentiality, any information you share with us.
  * We will limit the collection and use of your information to the minimum we require to deliver superior service to you, which includes advising you about our products and services and other opportunities, and to administer our business.
  * We will not reveal your information to any external organization (other than our Clients) unless we have previously informed you in disclosures, been authorized by you, or are required by law.
  * We will not use or share personal information for any purpose other than as disclosed in this Privacy Policy.
  * We will continuously assess ourselves to ensure that client privacy is respected.

## A special note about children’s privacy

Children are not eligible to use our services. You must be at least 18 years old to use this website and we ask that minors under the age of 18 do not submit any personal information to us. We do not knowingly collect, use or disclose personal information about visitors under 18 years of age.

## Information We Collect:

There are several areas on our website where you may be asked to enter both personal and non-personal information. Our website uses these input forms for clients and potential clients to request information about our products and services. We may also collect information in order to notify you about products, services, and other opportunities we think will be of interest to you. To make a request, individuals may be required to provide their contact information and personal information such as your name, address, phone number e-mail address, income and other financial or non-financial related information depending upon your expressed need (“Personal Information”).

Any information that you send to us may be collected and maintained in a file specific to you.

We also may collect demographic information. Demographic information is all other information such as gender, zip code, or any information that is not tied to your Personal Information. In addition, we might receive information about you from other sources (such as service providers) for tracking purposes. We may add the information we receive about you to your existing account. Like other websites, we also automatically receive and record certain types of information every time you visit us. We use “cookies” and other information to enhance your experience and present you with personalized offers. Likewise, we sometimes use third-party advertising companies to serve and track advertisements appearing on our website. These companies may employ cookies and action tags to measure advertising effectiveness. Any information that these third parties collect via cookies and action tags is completely anonymous. DegreeScout also employs software technology referred to as clear .gifs or “Web Bugs” which allow DegreeScout to determine which pieces of content on our site are most effective from a marketing standpoint. Clear .gifs work like cookies – they are graphics with a unique identifier which allow DegreeScout to track the online movement of visitors to our site. No personally identifiable information is tied to a clear gif. Clear gifs are also used in connection with our HTML-based emails to allow us to know when an email has been opened. If you do not wish to receive such email communications, please refer to the Opt Out policy below.

## How We Use Your Information:

The following paragraphs describe how we currently use Individual Information, but we may change or broaden its use at any time. As noted below, we may update this policy from time to time. We may use Individual Information to provide promotional offers to individuals by means of email advertising, telephone marketing, direct mail marketing, online banner advertising, and package stuffers, among other possible uses.

Services and Products Requests – If you submit a request for school information or other services offered by DegreeScout or any of its affiliated websites, DegreeScout will share the Personal Information contained in your input request form with our Clients strictly to process and fulfill your request. In some circumstances, DegreeScout may obtain additional information about you and/or share that information with our Clients.

Vendors – DegreeScout may share certain aggregated data with Clients of business partners and other third parties for general marketing and demographic purposes; however, this data does not include any of your personal identifying information. Although we require such entities to support our Privacy Policy, and to comply with applicable federal and state laws, we do not have any direct control over such entities nor do we guarantee or warrant their use and handling of such de-identified information.

Ads and Pop Ups – DegreeScout has relationships with a number of third party ad networks. From time to time you might receive advertisements for DegreeScout’s services from third parties. These advertisements are generated by a third party website that you have visited and are not generated or controlled by DegreeScout.

Affiliate Partners – Personal and business information submitted to DegreeScout and our Clients will be shared with third party service provider which operates our affiliate program.

As Permitted by Law – Please note that we reserve the right to disclose Personal Information for legal purposes, for the protection of this website, for the protection of DegreeScout (or any of its partners, employees, third party vendors, independent contractors or affiliates) and/or for the protection of other users of our website. Specifically, we reserve the right to disclose Personal Information as allowed by law or share your Personal Information with third parties if required by law to do so, or if we believe such action is necessary to either: (a) conform with the requirements of law enforcement or government agencies in response to subpoenas, court orders, federal/state audits or similar circumstances, or as otherwise required by law, (b) protect or defend our legal rights or property, this website, or other users of this website, or (c) investigate, prevent or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, or situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person. We may use an individual information for any legally permissible purpose in companyÕs sole discretion.

Special Note if you are Registered on a Do-Not-Call List – Our Clients may contact you by telephone, email, or mail based on the information you provided to us in order to process and fulfill your request, even if you have opted into the National Do Not Call List administered by the Federal Trade Commission, any state equivalent Do Not Call List, or the Do Not Call List of an internal company. If one of the Clients contacts you by telephone and you wish not to be contacted again by that that Client with respect to your inquiry, then you should specifically make a request to that Client not to contact you again. In the event a Client continues to contact you after you have instructed the Client to stop doing so, you should contact DegreeScout immediately to notify us of the problem.

## Security:

The security of your Personal Information is very important at DegreeScout and we take a number of steps to safeguard it and protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. Although DegreeScout uses industry standard efforts to safeguard the confidentiality of your personal identifiable information, such as firewalls and Secure Socket Layers, “perfect security” does not exist on the Internet.

## Links to Other Sites:

Please note that this website contains links and banner advertising that may direct you to other websites. In addition, you may have arrived at this website via a link or banner ad on a third party website. This Privacy Policy applies to all information that you provide to DegreeScout only. DegreeScout is not responsible for the privacy practices of or the content contained in other websites. When you use a link or a banner ad to go from this site to another website or vice versa, or are otherwise directed or redirected to another website, this Privacy Policy no longer applies. Your browsing and activity on such third party websites are subject to their own respective privacy policies, if any, which may differ from that of DegreeScout. In addition, the third party websites that you may visit or use to gain access to the DegreeScout website may request that you download software to take advantage of their offers. DegreeScout is not responsible for any product or service that you download, purchase, or otherwise receive in any manner or form, from a third party website. We encourage you to review the privacy policies of the third party websites that you enter and of any other service provider from whom you request services.

## Anti-Spam Policy:

You will not receive email communications and advertisements from DegreeScout or DegreeScout’s Clients unless you submit your email address to DegreeScout or to a Client. In order to receive email communication from DegreeScout and/or a Client, you must provide your email address. Providing your email address to either DegreeScout and/or any of its Clients represents your affirmative consent to receive such communications. Additionally, you may also receive emails that advertise DegreeScout services from third party publishers. We have strict policies for dealing with any third party email services to ensure that advertisements for DegreeScout are not sent out through a “Spam” mailing and to ensure that our offers are sent only to those individuals who have given us their email addresses. If you want to stop receiving emails from DegreeScout, a Client or a third party publisher, you should follow the opt-out instructions below or included in the Client or third party email so that you will not be included in any future mailings.

## Opt Out:

DegreeScout uses Individual Information to provide promotional offers by email to individuals. We may maintain separate email lists for different purposes. If email recipients wish to end their email subscription from a particular list, they need to follow the instructions at the end of each email message to unsubscribe from the particular list. To unsubscribe from all our email lists, a person must send an email: remove@DegreeScout.com. Our unsubscribe process impacts only the future delivery of electronic mailings disseminated by DegreeScout on its own behalf. You may still receive electronic mailings sent on behalf of Third Parties and your personal information may still be shared with Third Parties for use in offline marketing and data appends, including email appends.

You should also note that unsubscribing from our electronic mailings will not automatically unsubscribe the subscriber s information from any Third Party associates and licensees of the data. Since Third Party associates and licensee partners maintain separate databases from us, and you will need to unsubscribe from each source individually, if desired. This allows you the freedom to pick and choose which subscriptions to maintain and which to discontinue.

To exercise your right to opt out of having your Personal Information used for any purpose other than the service that you have specifically inquired about or requested, or if you would like to direct us not to make certain disclosures, please e-mail us or write to us with a detailed description of your request at the following address:

401 West A St, Suite 360  
San Diego, CA 92101  
remove@DegreeScout.com 

You may continue to receive email communications from us up to ten business days from the time we receive your unsubscribe request. Please note that DegreeScout can only control its own mailing list and policies. Third party advertisers that maintain their own mailing lists may send communications that advertise our services, and you may need to contact these parties directly in order to stop receiving their email communications. If you do not opt out, your Personal Information may be used as described in this Privacy Policy.

## Sale or Transfer to Third Parties.

DegreeScout MAY SELL OR TRANSFER INDIVIDUAL INFORMATION TO THIRD PARTIES FOR ANY PURPOSE IN ITS SOLE DISCRETION.

## Changes to this Privacy Policy:

DegreeScout may update or modify this Privacy Policy from time to time. If there are changes to this Privacy Policy, we will post such changes here. You will be notified if any of the material changes that affect the use of your Personal Information and asked to opt-in to the new use of your Personal Information. If you do not agree with the changes to how your information will be used, please do not continue to use this website. By using this site, you signify your assent to the DegreeScout Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to this Policy, please do not use any of the DegreeScout site. Please check the Policy each time you use our website to ensure you are aware of any changes in our privacy practices. Our Privacy Policy will indicate the date it was last updated. Your continued use of our site will signify your acceptance of the changes to our Privacy Policy.
